<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<items xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<item>
		<title>About The Artist</title>
		<subtitle>Jared Paul Wilson</subtitle>
		<description>&lt;font face="arial"&gt; &lt;p&gt;Jared Paul Wilson is recognized as an award winning professional Texas wildlife and western artist and published children's book author and illustrator.  Wilson grew up in a strong family environment that fostered his curiosity and desire to explore the world around him with all the beauty Texas countryside offers. He spent days traversing the outdoors and then would return to his house and fill pads of paper with all the amazing things he had encountered.  Overtime, Wilson's love for southern culture and wildlife combined with innate talent and a fertile imagination guided him to continue his studies at Midwestern State University where he graduated Cum Laude with a B.F.A.&lt;br&gt;  &lt;p&gt;As a professional, Wilson focuses on depicting Texas culture and the wildlife that inhabit its vast landscapes.  Staying true to the wonders of Texas and all its intricacies is a passion of Wilson.  He is extremely proud about his native Texas heritage and all aspects that make the Lone Star State both unique and beautiful.  In his artwork, Wilson strives to evoke a sense of feeling and connection with the viewer through each piece - a responsibility not taken lightly.  In order to truly capture the heart of the South, Wilson has traveled extensively, and his Prismacolor Premier pencils are merely a vessel depicting his heart's passion.&lt;br&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Wilson is a two-time cancer survivor and through his life-threatening battles awoke a burning passion to share his love for wildlife and western art with the world.  It is this brush with mortality that has driven the artist to maintain an unwavering and uncanny work ethic evident through his artwork.  Every day given is a gift from God and Jared Paul Wilson creates artwork in an effort to not waste a moment of it.  The artist was recently interviewed by international clothing brand UV Skinz in regards to his battles with cancer and his career as an artist, author and illustrator.&lt;br&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Working in Prismacolor Premier Soft Cored Pencils, Wilson generates a high level of meticulously photo realistic detail, texture and contrast within all of his masterpieces, a hallmark of Jared Paul Wilson artwork.  The artist is constantly pushing himself to discover new ways to manipulate the medium in order to achieve desired results.  The artist's goal is that the viewer not simply obtain an accurate and satisfying depiction of Texas living, but also experience the artwork and be drawn into the wildlife and western image.&lt;br&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Art by Jared Paul Wilson can be found in several private collections worldwide and his reputation as a wildlife and western artist is quickly building momentum.  With several exhibits and awards, Wilson has been featured on the cover of magazines such as Hill Country Sun and been interviewed on radio shows such as the Texas Wildlife Radio Show and the Financial Breeze (with listeners in over 100 countries).  Recently Wilson was profiled by Prismacolor, the internationally acclaimed company that produces the medium the artist uses when rendering his wildlife and western artworks.&lt;br&gt;  &lt;p&gt;In December 2009, Jared Paul Wilson married his wife, Erin, on the beautiful beaches of Fort Lauderdale, FL.  Erin is a native Minnesotan and the two currently reside in Lake Jackson, TX with their daughter, Lily Madison, and a beagle named Daisy.&lt;br&gt; &lt;/font&gt;</description>
		<image>http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-zhEyoOr8xzw/ULLU9tgGqhI/AAAAAAAAAA4/fjEJEouXSxs/s1600/The+Stockyards+2011.jpg</image>
		<group>Info &amp; Books</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Art Seminars</title>
		<subtitle>Information</subtitle>
		<description>&lt;font face="arial"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt; &lt;p&gt;  Award-winning Prismacolor art instructor, Jared Paul Wilson, offers two unique seminar experiences.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;  &lt;b&gt;1 Day Seminar:&lt;/b&gt; $75 per person with a 10 person minimum signed up for the course.  This class is an intensive crash course in Prismacolor pencils where Jared Paul Wilson teaches several different techniques for colored pencil artists ranging from beginner to expert.&lt;br&gt;  &lt;b&gt;3 Day Seminar:&lt;/b&gt; $200 per person with a 10 person minimum signed up for the course.  This class allows attendants the opportunity to learn several different techniques and begin a drawing of their choice to take with them and continue on their own.&lt;br&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Prismacolor Seminar Supplies:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;      Prismacolor Premier Soft Core Pencils (preferably a 48 set)&lt;br&gt;     Prismacolor Colorless Blender Pencil&lt;br&gt;     Sketchbook&lt;br&gt;     Pencil Sharpener&lt;br&gt;     Eraser&lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Schedule 2013 - 2014:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;      April 26, 2013 - &lt;br&gt;Delta Sigma Theta Sorority Mixer&lt;br&gt;     June 27, 2013 - &lt;br&gt;Albert Lea Art Center, 224 S. Broadway Ave., Albert Lea, MN 56007&lt;br&gt;     July 18 - 20, 2013 - &lt;br&gt;Brazosport Art League, 400 College Dr., Clute, TX  77531&lt;br&gt;     August 24, 2013 - &lt;br&gt;Conroe Art League, 127 Simonton St., Conroe, TX  77301&lt;br&gt;     October 12, 2013 - &lt;br&gt;Brownwood Art Association, 215 Fisk Av. Brownwood, TX  76801&lt;br&gt;     October 14, 2013 - &lt;br&gt;National Society of Artists, 5001 NASA Parkway, Seabrook, TX  77586&lt;br&gt;     November 9, 2013 - &lt;br&gt;National Society of Artist, 2nd Street Gallery, 1509½ 2nd St., Seabrook, TX  77586&lt;br&gt;     November 16, 2013 - &lt;br&gt;Conroe Art League, 127 Simonton St., Conroe, TX  77301&lt;br&gt;     February 6 - 8, 2014 - &lt;br&gt;Woodlands Art League, 25136 Grogans Park Dr., The Woodlands, TX  77380&lt;br&gt;     February 22, 2014 - &lt;br&gt;Fort Worth Community Arts Center, 1300 Gendy St., Fort Worth, TX  76107&lt;br&gt;     March 29, 2014 - &lt;br&gt;Fire House Gallery, 120 E. Garfield, Del Rio, TX  78840&lt;br&gt;     April 10, 2014 - &lt;br&gt;Brenham Art League, 112 West Alamo St., Brenham, TX  77833&lt;br&gt;     May 16 - 18, 2014  - &lt;br&gt;New Braunfels Art League, 239 W. San Antonio St., New Braunfels, TX 78130 &lt;br&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Pricing and information was last updated in this app November 2013. Please see &lt;a href="http://www.jaredpaulwilson.com/p/photo-mosaics.html" target=_blank&gt;the website&lt;/a&gt; for any updates and more information:&lt;br&gt; http://www.jaredpaulwilson.com  &lt;/font&gt;</description>
		<image>http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-tTyt5bGIsVo/UfB4bHnNUJI/AAAAAAAAAUM/VZ8PZfzbk5Q/s320/Delta+Sigma+Theta+Seminar.jpg</image>
		<group>Info &amp; Books</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Media and Awards</title>
		<subtitle>1999 - 2014</subtitle>
		<description>&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;font face="arial"&gt; &lt;p&gt;     Solo Exhibit at the Longview Museum of Fine Arts ~ &lt;br&gt;September - October 2014&lt;br&gt;     Solo Exhibit at the Del Rio Council for the Arts at the Firehouse ~ &lt;br&gt;March 2014&lt;br&gt;     Solo Exhibit at the Butler Longhorn Museum ~ &lt;br&gt;February 2014&lt;br&gt;     Victoria Art League Fall Art Show Second Place &amp; Third Place ~ &lt;br&gt;Fall 2013&lt;br&gt;     Light, Space &amp; Time Animal Art Exhibit (Special Merit) ~ &lt;br&gt;October 2013&lt;br&gt;     Brazoria County Fair Adult Art Juried Show (Fair Theme) ~ &lt;br&gt;Fall 2013&lt;br&gt;     Brazoria County Fair Adult Art Juried Show (Wildlife) ~ &lt;br&gt;Fall 2013&lt;br&gt;     Brazoria County Fair Adult Art Juried Show (Floral) ~ &lt;br&gt;Fall 2013&lt;br&gt;     Solo Exhibit at the Lake Jackson Public Library ~ &lt;br&gt;September - October 2013&lt;br&gt;     National Society of Artists 29th Annual Show ~ &lt;br&gt;Fall 2013&lt;br&gt;     Brazosport Center of the Arts &amp; Science Fall Juried Show Best of Show ~ &lt;br&gt;Fall 2013&lt;br&gt;     Solo Exhibit at the Brenham Heritage Museum ~ &lt;br&gt;September 2013&lt;br&gt;     Solo Exhibit at the Clute City Hall ~ &lt;br&gt;July - August 2013&lt;br&gt;     Solo Exhibit at the Lake Jackson City Hall ~ &lt;br&gt;May - June 2013&lt;br&gt;     Bay City Art League Juried Show (Professional Drawing) 1st, 2nd &amp; 3rd ~ &lt;br&gt;Spring 2013&lt;br&gt;     Brazosport Center of the Arts &amp; Science People's Choice 2nd Place  ~ &lt;br&gt;Spring 2013&lt;br&gt;     Solo Exhibit at the A. P. Beutel Building at DOW ~ &lt;br&gt;March - April 2013&lt;br&gt;     "Moments in Time" exhibit with Peter Janceke  ~ &lt;br&gt;January 2013&lt;br&gt;     National Society of Artists 28th Annual Show Barton Award  ~ &lt;br&gt;Winter 2012&lt;br&gt;     Brazoria County Fair Adult Art Juried Show Reserve Best of Show ~ &lt;br&gt;Fall 2012&lt;br&gt;     Brazoria County Fair Adult Art Juried Show Reserve Best of Class ~ &lt;br&gt;Fall 2012&lt;br&gt;     Brazoria County Fair Adult Art Juried Show (Western Theme) First Place ~ &lt;br&gt;Fall 2012&lt;br&gt;     Brazoria County Fair Adult Art Juried Show (Portrait) First Place ~ &lt;br&gt;Fall 2012&lt;br&gt;     Brazoria County Fair Adult Art Juried Show (Black &amp; White) First Place ~ &lt;br&gt;Fall 2012&lt;br&gt;     Galveston Art League Fall Juried Show First Place ~ &lt;br&gt;Fall 2012&lt;br&gt;     Brazosport Center of the Arts &amp; Science Fall Juried Show First Place ~ &lt;br&gt;Fall 2012&lt;br&gt;     Brazosport Center of the Arts &amp; Science Prismacolor 3 Day Seminar ~ &lt;br&gt;Summer 2012&lt;br&gt;     Brazosport Center of the Arts &amp; Science People's Choice 2nd Place ~ &lt;br&gt;Spring 2012&lt;br&gt;     Red Eye Art Show Fort Lauderdale (Accepted for gallery show) ~ &lt;br&gt;Fall 2006&lt;br&gt;     Art Institute of Fort Lauderdale Award Winning Scholarship Artwork ~ &lt;br&gt;Fall 2005&lt;br&gt;     Texas Intercollegiate Illustration First Place Award (2-D Art) ~ &lt;br&gt;Spring 2005&lt;br&gt;     Texas Intercollegiate Illustration Second Place Award (3-D Art) ~ &lt;br&gt;Spring 2005&lt;br&gt;     Published in Voices Magazine ~ &lt;br&gt;Spring 2004&lt;br&gt;     Fain Fine Arts Gallery Winner (Ceramics), Midwestern State University ~ &lt;br&gt;Spring 2004&lt;br&gt;     Fain Fine Arts Gallery Winner (Design), Midwestern State University ~ &lt;br&gt;Spring 2001&lt;br&gt;     Fain Foundation Art Scholarship ~ &lt;br&gt;2001 -2003&lt;br&gt;     12 County Art Show (Illustration), Texas Christian University ~ &lt;br&gt;Spring 1999&lt;br&gt; &lt;/font&gt;</description>
		<image>http://image.issuu.com/130114041015-565aff8f55df45359c331faf15473363/jpg/page_1_thumb_large.jpg</image>
		<group>Info &amp; Books</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Shoe Fly, Don't Bother Me</title>
		<subtitle>Written and Illustrated by Jared Paul Wilson</subtitle>
		<description>&lt;font face="arial"&gt; &lt;p&gt;A tiny fly lives happily within a pair of boots inside a local shoe store. The shoe fly is quite content with her life until a cowboy snatches up her lovely home and purchases it. The tiny fly follows the cowboy back to his farm in hopes of recovering her house. Upon reaching the farm, the shoe fly realizes she will need to find a new place to call home and, thus, starts her journey. The problem with her quest for a new home is that every time she asks one of the farm animals if she can live with them, the reply is always, “Shoe Fly, don’t bother me!” The fly realizes how important love and acceptance are as she searches for a new home. It isn’t until the bug meets a tired, old horse that the shoe fly’s fortune turns.  &lt;p&gt;The book can be ordered from http://www.jaredpaulwilson.com at &lt;a href="http://www.jaredpaulwilson.com/p/childrens-books.html" target=_blank&gt; this link&lt;/a&gt;, and you can even choose to get it autographed. &lt;p&gt;Booking Jared Paul Wilson&lt;br&gt; &lt;p&gt;To book Jared Paul Wilson at your school, please email your inquiry to jaredpaulwilson@gmail.com. We are also happy to answer questions or provide information by phone at (954) 632-3149.  However, all booking agreements must be made by email, which provides a communication trail and serves as a legally binding record of our event scheduling agreement. &lt;/font&gt;</description>
		<image>http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-PT7VgdlephM/ULLmMsFEHTI/AAAAAAAAABg/PzHoZO5s57M/s640/Show+Fly+lo+res.jpg</image>
		<group>Info &amp; Books</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Boots On</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Strathmore Paper, 11" x 17"</subtitle>
		<description>&lt;font face="arial"&gt; &lt;p&gt;"Well, they had a good, long run, the both of 'em.&lt;br&gt; And they went out with their boots on!"&lt;br&gt; - Secondhand Lions&lt;br&gt;  &lt;p&gt;"Boots On" was inspired while visiting the Fort Worth, TX Stock Yards, the only place in the world to hold two daily cattle drives.  After speaking with one of the older cowhands responsible with herding the Texas longhorns, I began to pay closer attention the clothes he was wearing, particularly his boots.  I immediately had the sensation, “If these boots could talk they would have plenty to share.”  It’s that sense of aged character I diligently aspired to leave evident in my drawing.  The boot within my artwork is clearly marred with wear and tear, scuffs and scrapes and dirt and grime - adorned like medals after years of hard work.&lt;br&gt;   &lt;p&gt;* Selected for the 2012 Galveston Art League Juried Art Show&lt;br&gt; * Selected for the 2012 National Society of Artists Fall Juried Show&lt;br&gt; * Featured on Prismacolor's website&lt;br&gt; &lt;/font&gt;</description>
		<image>http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-RhYU-loFB40/ULPqMcKg0jI/AAAAAAAAAEw/tiFfwXfkYrk/s1600/Boots+On.jpg</image>
		<group>Western Artwork Gallery</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Catch Me If You Can</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On 140 lbs Arches Watercolor Paper, 30" x 18"</subtitle>
		<image>http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-HmFJpFIzsBk/UmrW2X1QzGI/AAAAAAAAAZ4/0nsBAQ85S34/s400/Catch+Me+If+You+Can+small.jpg</image>
		<group>Western Artwork Gallery</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Cattle Drive</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Strathmore Paper, 24" x 16"</subtitle>
		<description>&lt;font face="arial"&gt; &lt;p&gt;* "Barton Award" 2012 National Society of Artists Fall Juried Show&lt;br&gt; * "Second Place" 2013 Bay City Art League Juried Show&lt;br&gt; * Featured on Prismacolor's website&lt;br&gt; * Printed in 2013 Texas Gulf Bank 100 Year Anniversary Coffee Book&lt;br&gt; &lt;/font&gt;</description>
		<image>http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-KvtNXl2k4ls/ULPqUCs6PuI/AAAAAAAAAE4/YfyM1LsvX98/s1600/Cattle+Drive.jpg</image>
		<group>Western Artwork Gallery</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Cattle Line</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Strathmore Paper, 12" x 18"</subtitle>
		<image>http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-x3gcrCdy_VU/ULPqaBXvjnI/AAAAAAAAAFA/Sp2PGqSsyrE/s1600/Cattle+Line.jpg</image>
		<group>Western Artwork Gallery</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Horse's Point of View</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Strathmore Paper, 11" x 17"</subtitle>
		<description>&lt;font face="arial"&gt; &lt;p&gt;"The way I see it, every time a man gets up in the morning he starts his life over. Sure, the bills are there to pay, and the job is there to do, but you don't have to stay in a pattern. You can always start over, saddle a fresh horse and take another trail."&lt;br&gt; - Louis L'Amour &lt;/font&gt;</description>
		<image>http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-GecrnBBnQZ0/ULPqluSeYcI/AAAAAAAAAFQ/AqqceR-xOXk/s1600/Horses+Point+of+View.jpg</image>
		<group>Western Artwork Gallery</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Live Like You Were Dying</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Strathmore Paper, 24" x 16"</subtitle>
		<description>&lt;font face="arial"&gt; &lt;p&gt;"I went sky divin', &lt;br&gt; I went rocky mountain climbin', &lt;br&gt; I went 2.7 seconds on a bull name Fumanchu.&lt;br&gt; And I loved deeper, &lt;br&gt; And I spoke sweeter, &lt;br&gt; And I gave forgiveness I've been denying, &lt;br&gt; And he said someday I hope you get the chance,&lt;br&gt; To live like you were dyin'."&lt;br&gt; - Tim McGraw, Live Like You Were Dying&lt;br&gt; &lt;/font&gt;</description>
		<image>http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-eU1D9LaPkX0/UUO96px_aGI/AAAAAAAAAKk/uPvKCnW0zgw/s400/Live+Like+You+Were+Dying+small.jpg</image>
		<group>Western Artwork Gallery</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Palo Duro Canyon Cowboy</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Strathmore Paper, 11" x 14"</subtitle>
		<description>&lt;font face="arial"&gt; &lt;p&gt;"Last night I couldn't sleep till after 4 in the morning — I had been out to the (Palo Duro) canyon all afternoon - till late at night - wonderful color - I wish I could tell you how big - and with the night the colors deeper and darker … I'm so glad I'm out here - I can't tell you how much I like it."&lt;br&gt; - Georgia O'Keeffe &lt;/font&gt;</description>
		<image>http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-8omp4Z3Di-I/ULPq0QCMnkI/AAAAAAAAAFk/3nVPOswYal4/s1600/Palo+Duro+Canyon+Cowboy.jpg</image>
		<group>Western Artwork Gallery</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Perched Upon Legacy</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Arches 140 lbs Watercolor Paper, 18" x 12"</subtitle>
		<description>&lt;font face="arial"&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Perched Upon Legacy” is an artistic interpretation of what so many share as the heart of the South,  the University of Texas.  With a mockingbird, the Texas state bird, resting upon the horn of a Texas longhorn, two iconic symbols are unified.  A burnt orange sky fills the backgroud as it rolls into the distance, suggesting there is more to this story.  From a design perspective, my purpose was to display brilliant light contrasting and complimenting the heavy darkness within the clouds.&lt;br&gt;   &lt;p&gt;* "Second Place" 2013 Victoria Art League Fall Art Show &lt;/font&gt;</description>
		<image>http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-U0iUTalVQBU/UjnclPGyJ7I/AAAAAAAAAWY/E9E0m0RThhA/s400/Perched+Upon+Legacy+small.jpg</image>
		<group>Western Artwork Gallery</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Rawhide Tough and Bull-Strong</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On 140 lbs Arches Watercolor Paper, 22" x 16"</subtitle>
		<description>&lt;font face="arial"&gt; &lt;p&gt;"Rawhide Tough and Bull-Strong" pays respect to the historic legacy of Parker Ranch and their unwavering resilience over 160 years on the island of Hawaii.  The artwork's title resonates far beyond the imagery depicted, reflecting Parker Ranch's commitment to maintaining traditions of family, loyalty and love of the land - momentous challenges for any privately owned ranch in modern times.  It is within artworks such as this, an artist grows both physically and emotionally as they breathe life into legacy. &lt;/font&gt;</description>
		<image>http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-9u7gBmAm6zk/Ump04_SH3OI/AAAAAAAAAZY/rnwvMYlkks4/s400/Rawhide+Tough+and+Bull+Strong+small.jpg</image>
		<group>Western Artwork Gallery</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Texas Longhorns</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Strathmore Paper, 18" x 12"</subtitle>
		<description>&lt;font face="arial"&gt; &lt;p&gt;* "First Place" 2012 Brazoria County Fair (Western) &lt;/font&gt;</description>
		<image>http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-_Sczl9lZRtc/ULPqvN2Z0pI/AAAAAAAAAFc/7qSCaLs2W7Q/s1600/Longhorn.jpg</image>
		<group>Western Artwork Gallery</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>The Only Way I Know</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Strathmore Paper, 11" x 17"</subtitle>
		<description>&lt;font face="arial"&gt; &lt;p&gt;"That’s the only way I know&lt;br&gt; Don’t stop 'til everything’s gone&lt;br&gt; Straight ahead, never turn round&lt;br&gt; Don’t back up, don’t back down&lt;br&gt; Full throttle, wide open&lt;br&gt; You get tired and you don’t show it&lt;br&gt; Dig a little deeper when you think&lt;br&gt; you can’t dig no more&lt;br&gt; That’s the only way I know"&lt;br&gt; - Jason Aldean, The Only Way I Know&lt;br&gt; &lt;p&gt;  * "Second Place" at Brazosport Center 2013 People's Choice&lt;br&gt; * Printed in 2013 Texas Gulf Bank 100 Year Anniversary Coffee Book&lt;br&gt; * "First Place" 2013 Brazoria County Fair (Fair Theme)&lt;br&gt; &lt;/font&gt;</description>
		<image>http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-0JNLZiQxFd4/UTuy7SlnazI/AAAAAAAAAKM/tmYILccngag/s400/The+Only+Way+I+Know+small.jpg</image>
		<group>Western Artwork Gallery</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Wrong Side of the Law</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Strathmore Paper, 32" x 40"</subtitle>
		<description>&lt;font face="arial"&gt; &lt;p&gt;Having viewed several Western films over the years, “Wrong Side of the Law” truly embodies the glamour of Hollywood blended with whispers of fact.  While this artwork certainly contains theatrical undertones – at it’s core, this drawing is a dramatic revelation between right and wrong.  The perspective provided offers a glimpse of a showdown between a Texas Ranger and an assumed outlaw.  The winner of this duel is intentionally left to the viewer’s interpretation; however, hand positioning may suggests otherwise.  The striking color, perspective and grit leave this artwork a memorable and creative portrayal of the artist’s romanitc love for justice within the wild west.&lt;br&gt;  &lt;p&gt;* Selected for the 2013 Brazosport Center Fall Juried Show&lt;br&gt; * "Third Place" 2013 Victoria Art League Fall Art Show&lt;br&gt; &lt;/font&gt;</description>
		<image>http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-qXH6-TL5x24/Ue_vGQ2ji1I/AAAAAAAAATo/UJsRJqhEmR0/s400/Wrong+Side+of+the+Law+small.jpg</image>
		<group>Western Artwork Gallery</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Yesterday's Rain</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Strathmore Paper, 16" x 20"</subtitle>
		<description>&lt;font face="arial"&gt; &lt;p&gt;"I don't care what the future holds&lt;br&gt; And don't care about what you've been told&lt;br&gt; Don't want to hear what the weatherman has to say&lt;br&gt; 'Cause I'm standing knee deep in yesterday's rain"&lt;br&gt; - Toby Keith, Yesterday's Rain&lt;br&gt;   &lt;p&gt;“Yesterday's gone on down the river and you can't get it back.”&lt;br&gt; - Larry McMurtry, Lonesome Dove&lt;br&gt;  &lt;p&gt;* Featured in Hill Country Sun Magazine January 2013 &lt;/font&gt;</description>
		<image>http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-458BiXg4fSk/ULPq_xDDBRI/AAAAAAAAAFs/KvdfPgJZSnk/s1600/Yesterday%27s+Rain.jpg</image>
		<group>Western Artwork Gallery</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Backyard Trails</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Strathmore Paper, 16.5" x 16.5"</subtitle>
		<description>&lt;font face="arial"&gt; &lt;p&gt;"Backyard Trails" is viewed through the timeless perspective of my in-laws beautiful backyard.  I prepare fairly exhaustive studies of the Southwest before beginning work on my wildlife drawings, but this piece is a rarity for me due to the lack of snow available to influence the majority of my artworks.  This particular artwork is the combination of several images superimposed with sharp contrast illuminating the slope beyond the snowdrift-covered creek where the deer make their way across the landscape.   A unique aspect of this artwork is the animal tracks intersecting spontaneously throughout the foreground, suggesting a story that stretches beyond the image.&lt;br&gt;  &lt;p&gt;* Featured in Hill Country Sun Magazine January 2013 &lt;/font&gt;</description>
		<image>http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-jQnfh2aFwbk/ULPWtfwNdSI/AAAAAAAAAC0/JHaO1P7HK5w/s1600/Backyard+Trails.jpg</image>
		<group>Wildlife Artwork Gallery</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Bird's Eye View</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Strathmore Paper, 20" x 16"</subtitle>
		<description>&lt;font face="arial"&gt; &lt;p&gt;I have long been fascinated by birds of prey, particularly Red-tailed Hawks, which are a hallmark throughout North America.  I have always lived and traveled in and around the rural countryside where it’s not uncommon for your only company to be a bird of prey, a lone speckled spot soaring across a big Texas sky.  The challenge in this piece was balancing the impressive beauty and color palette with the fierce and deadly characteristics known of raptors and then orchestrate that into a harmonious composition.&lt;br&gt;  &lt;p&gt;* Featured on Prismacolor's website&lt;br&gt; * "Third Place" 2013 Bay City Art League Juried Show&lt;br&gt; &lt;/font&gt;</description>
		<image>http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-qqElcV57yhw/UUO0R1x2aEI/AAAAAAAAAKY/RPvzgm0ghbk/s400/Birds+Eye+View+small.jpg</image>
		<group>Wildlife Artwork Gallery</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Curious Coon</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Strathmore Paper, 18" x 12"</subtitle>
		<description>&lt;font face="arial"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The predictably bold curiosity of raccoons brings a smile to my face, but their nocturnal clock and sneaky personality leave them frustratingly elusive to my photography.  That all changed when a desperate high school senior that needed to pass my art class asked if there was anything he could do for extra credit.  He agreed to assist me in acquiring some raccoon photographs.  The next morning I was shocked as I entered my classroom to see a well fed raccoon sitting in a cage.  After thoroughly documenting the coon, which I named Roger, he was rewarded with a treat and released into the wild.  My goal in this artwork is to communicate the inquisitive and comical nature of the intelligent mammal while evoking a sense of connection with the viewer through their loveable and deceptive pet like resemblance.&lt;/font&gt;</description>
		<image>http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-5TgJMVTRWSw/ULPXGLSm4qI/AAAAAAAAADU/pAct7BX53l0/s1600/Curious+Coon.jpg</image>
		<group>Wildlife Artwork Gallery</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Deer Friends</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Strathmore Paper, 14" x 11"</subtitle>
		<image>http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-u9z7L9gNxNM/ULPXMyDFHLI/AAAAAAAAADc/r7QjWjN1hxk/s1600/Deer+Friends.jpg</image>
		<group>Wildlife Artwork Gallery</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Feeding Fawn</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Strathmore Paper, 12" x 18"</subtitle>
		<description>&lt;font face="arial"&gt; &lt;p&gt;"Love is a song that never ends&lt;br&gt; Life may be swift and fleeting&lt;br&gt; Hope may die yet love's beautiful music&lt;br&gt; Comes each day like the dawn&lt;br&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Love is a song that never ends&lt;br&gt; One simple theme repeating&lt;br&gt; Like the voice of a heavenly choir&lt;br&gt; Love's sweet music flows on"&lt;br&gt; - Composed by Larry Morey, Love is a Song&lt;br&gt;   Main Title of Bambi&lt;br&gt; &lt;/font&gt;</description>
		<image>http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-dgu3T6xOLyE/ULPXYzq7_hI/AAAAAAAAADk/Ta8i_gQMCrY/s1600/Feeding+Fawn.jpg</image>
		<group>Wildlife Artwork Gallery</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Fuzzy Fawn</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Strathmore Paper, 24" x 16"</subtitle>
		<description>&lt;font face="arial"&gt; &lt;p&gt; I frequently draw deer in my wildlife artworks, and always enjoy capturing their elegant silhouettes.  In the encounter that inspired this drawing, I was fortunate to obtain the unmatched beauty of a resting fawn tucked away in the foliage as daylight dimmed. Emotion is certainly evoked as the tiny deer reflects something more like a pet or stuffed animal a child might grasp.  It is within “Fuzzy Fawn” that the viewer may search within the deer’s eyes and come face to face with himself or herself.&lt;br&gt; &lt;p&gt;* "Second Place" Brazosport Center 2012 People's Choice&lt;br&gt; * "First Place" 2012 Galveston Art League Juried Art Show&lt;br&gt; * Cover Art for Hill Country Sun Magazine January 2013&lt;br&gt; &lt;/font&gt;</description>
		<image>http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-LnPDFbXYVyU/ULPXeHqQu2I/AAAAAAAAADs/XQfGf5xCv50/s1600/Fuzzy+Fawn.jpg</image>
		<group>Wildlife Artwork Gallery</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Glimpse of Beauty</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Strathmore Paper, 11" x 17"</subtitle>
		<description>&lt;font face="arial"&gt; &lt;p&gt;During a recent trip to a Texas State Park, I experienced dreadful weather and unimaginable misfortune as I pursued new reference material for future artworks.  I was cleaning up my campsite on the final day when I noticed a beautiful cardinal resting in the branches of an old oak tree.  I grabbed my camera and was able to capture one quick shot.  Then, in the blink of an eye, the bird was gone.  It is through this momentary flash of nature’s majesty that I came up with the title of this artwork, "Glimpse of Beauty."  Within this drawing I dramatically enhanced the blurred vision of branches framing the bird, suggesting even this created artwork is fleeting. &lt;/font&gt;</description>
		<image>http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-liZUc6BwLug/ULPXA8CEjTI/AAAAAAAAADM/WdIl_whMOLg/s1600/Brazosbend+State+Park+Cardinal.jpg</image>
		<group>Wildlife Artwork Gallery</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Gulf Coast Seagulls</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Strathmore Paper, 11" x 17"</subtitle>
		<description>&lt;font face="arial"&gt; &lt;p&gt;Seagulls have long been a favorite bird for me to observe.  Living on the Texas coast, I have come to view ocean and seagulls as synonymous.  It’s my observations and enjoyment of seagulls, which eventually led to this particular artwork.  The two gulls are strikingly similar in contrast to the rolling waves behind them, but on closer observation it is strangely apparent that one of the seagulls is missing a leg.  The coastal bird is known for losing their legs through horrific, but sadly all too common action by vacationers, where they offer food in one hand and then attempt to grab the bird when they fly close enough.  The blurred ocean waves and undisguised pencil work in the background are the abstract suggestion to the frailty and impermanence of life. &lt;/font&gt;</description>
		<image>http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-XqI6OVh9mUg/ULPXjBwgIvI/AAAAAAAAAD0/9hC7uWQUAV0/s1600/Gulf+Coast+Seagulls.jpg</image>
		<group>Wildlife Artwork Gallery</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Homage to the Bluebonnet</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Strathmore Paper, 11" x 17"</subtitle>
		<description>&lt;font face="arial"&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Blue is the emblem of loyalty,&lt;br&gt; They're as blue as the deep, deep sea,&lt;br&gt; Their smiling faces bring gladness,&lt;br&gt; For they bloom for your and for me.&lt;br&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Bluebonnets, so gorgeous and stately,&lt;br&gt; In your mantle of blue and of green,&lt;br&gt; In the spring when you're in your full glory,&lt;br&gt; You're the loveliest sight ever seen.&lt;br&gt;  &lt;p&gt;You're beautiful when you sway in the sunshine,&lt;br&gt; You look like waves of the sea,&lt;br&gt; Ah, Texas was wise in her choice of flow'r,&lt;br&gt; So we offer our homage to thee."&lt;br&gt; - Julia D. Booth &amp; Lora C. Crockett&lt;br&gt;  &lt;p&gt;* 2013 Brazoria County Fair (Floral)&lt;br&gt;&lt;/font&gt;</description>
		<image>http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-I0TtiozhuNg/ULPW6BklgAI/AAAAAAAAADE/_hNq-s-W_Vk/s1600/Bluebonnet+2.jpg</image>
		<group>Wildlife Artwork Gallery</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Knee Deep</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Arches 140 lbs Paper, 16" x 28"</subtitle>
		<description>&lt;font face="arial"&gt; &lt;p&gt;"Mind on a permanent vacation&lt;br&gt; The ocean is my only medication&lt;br&gt; Wishing my condition ain't ever gonna go away"&lt;br&gt; - Zac Brown Band, Knee Deep &lt;/font&gt;</description>
		<image>http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-UhdntC7jn2s/UYhCj7sv0kI/AAAAAAAAALc/5-yakLE0psM/s400/Knee+Deep+small.jpg</image>
		<group>Wildlife Artwork Gallery</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Lantanas</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Strathmore Paper, 11" x 17"</subtitle>
		<description>&lt;font face="arial"&gt; This piece is reflective of an experience I had on my first trip to Rockport, TX.  I had created several floral artworks that had garnered a lot of interest, but I expected the coastal town of Rockport to provide me with gulf coast images, leaving me pleasantly surprised when I discovered a beautiful cemetery filled with flowers of all types.  I was stunned at the level of color and life that was in full bloom encased within an environment associated with death and mourning.  Visually, the contrast between the "Lantana's" bright and simplistic petals and the dramatically dark leaf patterns offer the same subtle sense of restfulness and peace I encountered as I first documented this beautiful cemetery. &lt;/font&gt;</description>
		<image>http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-Fp_aUkU-o5k/ULPXokx4_aI/AAAAAAAAAEA/Wscv6heg2uc/s1600/Lantanas.jpg</image>
		<group>Wildlife Artwork Gallery</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Like A Bird On A Wire</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Strathmore Paper, 14" x 10"</subtitle>
		<description>&lt;font face="arial"&gt; &lt;p&gt;"Like a bird on a wire&lt;br&gt; Like a drunk in a midnight choir&lt;br&gt; I have tried in my way to be free"&lt;br&gt; - Johnny Cash, Bird on a Wire&lt;br&gt; &lt;/font&gt;</description>
		<image>http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-ltVZme5Xwxk/UVXCHv_i2GI/AAAAAAAAAK4/hqTW_bKXsxI/s400/Like+A+Bird+On+A+Wire+small.jpg</image>
		<group>Wildlife Artwork Gallery</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Lore of the Bluebonnet</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Strathmore Paper, 11" x 17"</subtitle>
		<description>&lt;font face="arial"&gt; &lt;p&gt;"Backyard Trails" is viewed through the timeless perspective of my in-laws beautiful backyard.  I prepare fairly exhaustive studies of the Southwest before beginning work on my wildlife drawings, but this piece is a rarity for me due to the lack of snow available to influence the majority of my artworks.  This particular artwork is the combination of several images superimposed with sharp contrast illuminating the slope beyond the snowdrift-covered creek where the deer make their way across the landscape.   A unique aspect of this artwork is the animal tracks intersecting spontaneously throughout the foreground, suggesting a story that stretches beyond the image.&lt;br&gt;  &lt;p&gt;* Featured in Hill Country Sun Magazine January 2013 &lt;/font&gt;</description>
		<image>http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-QlqGA7agjZk/ULPWzoEKSQI/AAAAAAAAAC8/MgUGXAXGCJ0/s1600/Bluebonnet+1.jpg</image>
		<group>Wildlife Artwork Gallery</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Poor Man's Pig</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Strathmore Paper, 20" x 16"</subtitle>
		<description>&lt;font face="arial"&gt; &lt;p&gt;Armadillos are known as “Poor Man’s Pig” throughout the South.  I was on my way back to the campsite at Brazos Bend State Park when an armadillo nonchalantly strolled past, nose buried in the foliage by my boots.  Apparently, mealtime was a bigger concern than the presence of a hiker.  I began snapping several photos of the armadillo blanketed in the evening light.  Between photographs the surrounding trees shifted colors as the sun set, offering a new canvas of colors.  From an artistic standpoint, I enjoyed exploring the wonderful variety of color and texture in this piece, from the armadillo’s intricate armored pattern, to the colorful leafs, to the setting sun’s light.&lt;br&gt; &lt;p&gt;* Featured in Hill Country Sun Magazine January 2013&lt;br&gt; * "First Place" 2013 Brazoria County Fair (Wildlife)&lt;br&gt; &lt;/font&gt;</description>
		<image>http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-xpy2Eb26xzw/ULPX73w1T4I/AAAAAAAAAEY/Z8wcvyyUiqs/s1600/Texas+Armadillo.jpg</image>
		<group>Wildlife Artwork Gallery</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Prickly Pear Cactus</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Strathmore Paper, 11" x 17"</subtitle>
		<description>&lt;font face="arial"&gt; &lt;p&gt;Former vice president John Nance Garner, also known as “Cactus Jack,” so eloquently extolled the virtues of the cactus, from its hardy durability to its orchid-like beautiful flowers.  It was during a trip to Aledo, TX, I stumbled upon a gorgeous prickly pear cactus and understood why Mr. Garner was so passionate about that particular plant.  The cactus interpreted in this artwork stood tall as I documented it, wearing a crown that glowed in the hot afternoon sunlight.   I made it my mission to illuminate this cactus in a noble effort to offer others a similar experience.  The tendrils of blurred color cutting through the cactus and bleached background further enhance the depth of field, setting the cactus apart from its surroundings.&lt;br&gt; &lt;p&gt; * "First Place" 2012 Brazosport Center Fall Juried Show&lt;br&gt; * Featured on Prismacolor's website&lt;br&gt; &lt;/font&gt;</description>
		<image>http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-KkeFNAP0uKo/ULPXvClDUeI/AAAAAAAAAEI/BwzYIYOjklo/s1600/Prickly+Pear+Cactus.jpg</image>
		<group>Wildlife Artwork Gallery</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Tattered Butterfly</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Strathmore Paper, 24" x 16"</subtitle>
		<description>&lt;font face="arial"&gt; &lt;p&gt;* Featured on Prismacolor's website&lt;br&gt; * "First Place" 2013 Bay City Art League Juried Show &lt;/font&gt;</description>
		<image>http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-u-h7sudBWXE/ULPX09ZhfZI/AAAAAAAAAEQ/UcIa3ZPtYE8/s1600/Tattered+Butterfly.jpg</image>
		<group>Wildlife Artwork Gallery</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>The Mockingbird - A True Texan</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Arches 140 lbs Paper, 20" x 16"</subtitle>
		<description>&lt;font face="arial"&gt; &lt;p&gt;"The mockingbird is found in all parts of the State, in winter and in summer, in the city and in the country, on the prairie and in the woods and hills...is a singer of distinctive type, a fighter for the protection of his home, falling, if need be, in its defense, like any true Texan..."&lt;br&gt; - The Texas Legislature 1927 &lt;/font&gt;</description>
		<image>http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-cxnz45eooFI/Ub0dVBKcYBI/AAAAAAAAASs/TCiUmMNRC4o/s400/The+Mockingbird+A+Texan+Tried+and+True+small.jpg</image>
		<group>Wildlife Artwork Gallery</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Wildflower Sunburst</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Strathmore Paper, 11" x 17"</subtitle>
		<image>http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-rMKfZPGVdVI/ULPYCHt4WaI/AAAAAAAAAEg/hDnpkfsU4ac/s1600/Wildflower+Sunburst.jpg</image>
		<group>Wildlife Artwork Gallery</group>
	</item>
</items>