<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<items xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<item>
		<title>Homage to the Bluebonnet</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Strathmore Paper</subtitle>
		<description>Blue is the emblem of loyalty, They're as blue as the deep, deep sea, Their smiling faces bring gladness, For they bloom for your and for me. Bluebonnets, so gorgeous and stately, In your mantle of blue and of green, In the spring when you're in your full glory, You're the loveliest sight ever seen. You're beautiful when you sway in the sunshine, You look like waves of the sea, Ah, Texas was wise in her choice of flow'r, So we offer our homage to thee. - Julia D. Booth &amp; Lora C. Crockett *2013 Brazoria County Fair (Floral)</description>
		<image>http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-I0TtiozhuNg/ULPW6BklgAI/AAAAAAAAADE/_hNq-s-W_Vk/s1600/Bluebonnet+2.jpg</image>
		<group>Artwork - Wildlife</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Curious Coon</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Strathmore Paper</subtitle>
		<description>The predictably bold curiosity of raccoons brings a smile to my face, but their nocturnal clock and sneaky personality leave them frustratingly elusive to my photography.  That all changed when a desperate high school senior that needed to pass my art class asked if there was anything he could do for extra credit.  He agreed to assist me in acquiring some raccoon photographs.  The next morning I was shocked as I entered my classroom to see a well fed raccoon sitting in a cage.  After thoroughly documenting the coon, which I named Roger, he was rewarded with a treat and released into the wild.  My goal in this artwork is to communicate the inquisitive and comical nature of the intelligent mammal while evoking a sense of connection with the viewer through their loveable and deceptive pet like resemblance.</description>
		<image>http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-5TgJMVTRWSw/ULPXGLSm4qI/AAAAAAAAADU/pAct7BX53l0/s1600/Curious+Coon.jpg</image>
		<group>Artwork - Wildlife</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Feeding Fawn</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Strathmore Paper</subtitle>
		<description>Love is a song that never ends Life may be swift and fleeting Hope may die yet love's beautiful music Comes each day like the dawn Love is a song that never ends One simple theme repeating Like the voice of a heavenly choir Love's sweet music flows on - Composed by Larry Morey, Love is a Song, Main Title of Bambi</description>
		<image>http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-dgu3T6xOLyE/ULPXYzq7_hI/AAAAAAAAADk/Ta8i_gQMCrY/s1600/Feeding+Fawn.jpg</image>
		<group>Artwork - Wildlife</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Shoe Fly, Don't Bother Me</title>
		<subtitle>Written and Illustrated by Jared Paul Wilson</subtitle>
		<description>A tiny fly lives happily within a pair of boots inside a local shoe store. The shoe fly is quite content with her life until a cowboy snatches up her lovely home and purchases it. The tiny fly follows the cowboy back to his farm in hopes of recovering her house. Upon reaching the farm, the shoe fly realizes she will need to find a new place to call home and, thus, starts her journey. The problem with her quest for a new home is that every time she asks one of the farm animals if she can live with them, the reply is always, “Shoe Fly, don’t bother me!” The fly realizes how important love and acceptance are as she searches for a new home. It isn’t until the bug meets a tired, old horse that the shoe fly’s fortune turns. Note: The book can be ordered from http://www.jaredpaulwilson.com/p/childrens-books.html, and you can choose autograph personalization.</description>
		<image>http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-PT7VgdlephM/ULLmMsFEHTI/AAAAAAAAABg/PzHoZO5s57M/s640/Show+Fly+lo+res.jpg</image>
		<group>Children's Books</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Boots On</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Strathmore Paper</subtitle>
		<description>Boots On was inspired while visiting the Fort Worth, TX Stock Yards, the only place in the world to hold two daily cattle drives.  After speaking with one of the older cowhands responsible with herding the Texas longhorns, I began to pay closer attention the clothes he was wearing, particularly his boots.  I immediately had the sensation, “If these boots could talk they would have plenty to share.”  It’s that sense of aged character I diligently aspired to leave evident in my drawing.  The boot within my artwork is clearly marred with wear and tear, scuffs and scrapes and dirt and grime - adorned like medals after years of hard work. * Selected for the 2012 Galveston Art League Juried Art Show * Selected for the 2012 National Society of Artists Fall Juried Show * Featured on Prismacolor's website</description>
		<image>http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-RhYU-loFB40/ULPqMcKg0jI/AAAAAAAAAEw/tiFfwXfkYrk/s1600/Boots+On.jpg</image>
		<group>Artwork - Western</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Perched Upon Legacy</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Arches 140 lbs Watercolor Paper</subtitle>
		<description>“Perched Upon Legacy” is an artistic interpretation of what so many share as the heart of the South,  the University of Texas.  With a mockingbird, the Texas state bird, resting upon the horn of a Texas longhorn, two iconic symbols are unified.  A burnt orange sky fills the backgroud as it rolls into the distance, suggesting there is more to this story.  From a design perspective, my purpose was to display brilliant light contrasting and complimenting the heavy darkness within the clouds. * "Second Place" 2013 Victoria Art League Fall Art Show</description>
		<image>http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-U0iUTalVQBU/UjnclPGyJ7I/AAAAAAAAAWY/E9E0m0RThhA/s400/Perched+Upon+Legacy+small.jpg</image>
		<group>Artwork - Western</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Wrong Side of the Law</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Strathmore Paper</subtitle>
		<description>Having viewed several Western films over the years, “Wrong Side of the Law” truly embodies the glamour of Hollywood blended with whispers of fact.  While this artwork certainly contains theatrical undertones – at it’s core, this drawing is a dramatic revelation between right and wrong.  The perspective provided offers a glimpse of a showdown between a Texas Ranger and an assumed outlaw.  The winner of this duel is intentionally left to the viewer’s interpretation; however, hand positioning may suggests otherwise.  The striking color, perspective and grit leave this artwork a memorable and creative portrayal of the artist’s romanitc love for justice within the wild west. * Selected for the 2013 Brazosport Center Fall Juried Show * "Third Place" 2013 Victoria Art League Fall Art Show</description>
		<image>http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-qXH6-TL5x24/Ue_vGQ2ji1I/AAAAAAAAATo/UJsRJqhEmR0/s400/Wrong+Side+of+the+Law+small.jpg</image>
		<group>Artwork - Western</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Palo Duro Canyon Cowboy</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Strathmore Paper</subtitle>
		<description>Last night I couldn't sleep till after 4 in the morning — I had been out to the (Palo Duro) canyon all afternoon - till late at night - wonderful color - I wish I could tell you how big - and with the night the colors deeper and darker … I'm so glad I'm out here - I can't tell you how much I like it. - Georgia O'Keeffe</description>
		<image>http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-8omp4Z3Di-I/ULPq0QCMnkI/AAAAAAAAAFk/3nVPOswYal4/s1600/Palo+Duro+Canyon+Cowboy.jpg</image>
		<group>Artwork - Western</group>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Lantanas</title>
		<subtitle>Prismacolor On Strathmore Paper</subtitle>
		<description>This piece is reflective of an experience I had on my first trip to Rockport, TX.  I had created several floral artworks that had garnered a lot of interest, but I expected the coastal town of Rockport to provide me with gulf coast images, leaving me pleasantly surprised when I discovered a beautiful cemetery filled with flowers of all types.  I was stunned at the level of color and life that was in full bloom encased within an environment associated with death and mourning.  Visually, the contrast between the "Lantana's" bright and simplistic petals and the dramatically dark leaf patterns offer the same subtle sense of restfulness and peace I encountered as I first documented this beautiful cemetery.</description>
		<image>http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-Fp_aUkU-o5k/ULPXokx4_aI/AAAAAAAAAEA/Wscv6heg2uc/s1600/Lantanas.jpg</image>
		<group>Artwork - Wildlife</group>
	</item>
</items>